<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on PEIKE PATRICK LI</title>
    <link>https://peikeli.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on PEIKE PATRICK LI</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018-{year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://peikeli.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>JEN-1</title>
      <link>https://peikeli.github.io/project/jen-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peikeli.github.io/project/jen-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Music generation has attracted growing interest with the advancement of deep generative models. However, generating music conditioned on textual descriptions, known as text-to-music, remains challenging due to the complexity of musical structures and high sampling rate requirements. Despite the task&amp;rsquo;s significance, prevailing generative models exhibit limitations in music quality, computational efficiency, and generalization. This paper introduces JEN-1, a universal high-fidelity model for text-to-music generation. JEN-1 is a diffusion model incorporating both autoregressive and non-autoregressive training. Through in-context learning, JEN-1 performs various generation tasks including text-guided music generation, music inpainting, and continuation. Evaluations demonstrate JEN-1&amp;rsquo;s superior performance over state-of-the-art methods in text-music alignment and music quality while maintaining computational efficiency. Our demos are available at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.futureverse.com/research/jen/demos/jen1&#34;&gt;https://www.futureverse.com/research/jen/demos/jen1&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
